Willard Mullin Cartoons
Willard Mullin Cartoons
- Track and Field cartoons, 9
  - The Heavy Artillery, 1961-1966; key words: Randy Matson, shot put, Texas A and M, Drake Relays (Box 3)
  - In The Clear, 1961-1966; key words: Bob Seagren, pole vault, Millrose Games (Box 3)
  - The Natural, 1961-1966; key words: Valery Brumel, high jump, NYAC Meet (Box 3)
  - On Your Mark…, 1961-1966; key words: AAU, NCAA, sanctioning authority (Box 3)
  - One For The Money, 1964; key words: long jump, AAU National Meet, 1964 Olympic team (Box 3)
  - [That Catapult They Use…], 1961-1966; key words: John Pennel, pole vault (Box 3)
- Misc. Sports cartoons, 13
  - Agenda For 1964, key words: artist as infant reading list (Box 3)
  - …And, Among Other Things, 1964; key words: 81st National Horse Show, LBJ, Goldwater (Box 3)
  - Drawing Board Re-Visited, 1961-1966; key words: various New York sports figures, Willard Mullin returning from vacation (Box 3)
  - Go! I Said, 1961-1966; key words: Mets, New York horse racing, the New Breed (Box 3)
  - The Groaning Board, 1961-1966; key words: Yankees, Rangers, Jets, Giants, Knicks, Mets, Pa Knickerbocker (Box 3)
  - A Jolly Trio, 1961-1966; key words: Rangers, Knicks, boxer, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - [Last Year Chuck McKinley…], 1964; key words: Chuck McKinley, Wimbledon, Tennis (Box 3)
  - Objective Tokyo, 1963; key words: 80th National Horse Show, Mary Mairs, Tokyo Olympics (Box 3)
  - Panning Out Pretty Good, 1964; key words: Uncle Sam, Mt. Fujiyama, Tokyo Olympics (Box 3)
  - Pot-Pourri, 1964; key words: Yankees, Mets, Giants, Jets, and misc. NY sports figures, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - That Commodity Called Youth, 1964; key words: Scott Ethan Allen, Men's figure skating (Box 3)
  - To Each His Own…, 1961-1966; key words: various sports, horses, camel racing, horseshoes, figure skating (Box 3)
  - Voice From Astern, 1961-1966; key words: Constellation, yachting (Box 3)